emergencyreporting.com 2016-05-04

# Privacy Policy - Emergency Reporting

### Overview

Emergency Reporting respects your privacy and takes great care to safeguard information in our possession. The company does not share customer information without permission, unless we are legally required to do so.

We restrict access to your information only to those individuals within the company who need it to provide you with services. This may include your account activation process, account support, and service news updates.

Any third-party companies contracted to provide services are required to keep your information secure and confidential.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as email, or participate in another site feature.

When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

To quickly process your transactions.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

If you have opted-in to receive our email newsletter, we may send you periodic emails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional email from us, please use the “Unsubscribe” link in the email or contact us at [marketing@emergencyreporting.com](mailto:marketing@emergencyreporting.com) if you have any problems. If you have not opted-in to receive email newsletters, you will not receive these emails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and trainings will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our email list and receive email communications from us.

### How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

### Policy Questions

For more information about our privacy policy, call us toll free at: 1-866-773-7678 or by email at [info@emergencyreporting.com](mailto:info@emergencyreporting.com).

#### __Newsletter

Enter your e-mail below to subscribe to our free newsletter.  We promise not to bother you often!
